<resources>
    <string name="app_name">App-a-thon Hack</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="main_text">App-A-Thon \n\n

        Main Page: \n\t
        User should select either client or doctor.\n\t
        If select client then it can enter a new form, else he can also see other prescriptions of other people with the same problems.\n\t
        If select doctor then he can see all the submitted forms and he can answer to their problems.\n\t
        He can also visit some nearby hospitals\n\n

        New Application:\n
        Patient has to enter his/her details for submitting the form including their problems.\n\t

        Doctor details:\n\t
        He can see all the list of forms that have been submitted so far.\n\t
        He can categorise based on the type of the problems.\n\t
        He can also sort it on the basis of date modified\n\n

        Patient details:\n\t
        Patient\'s info\n\n

        Checking mechanism:\n\t
        It includes blood pressure, heart-beat rate, blood viscosity, oxygen level , pulse wave etc which can be used to detect the problems or diseases
        which can be present in humans based on machine learning and artificial algorithms.\n\t
        Once detected by the algorithms, it will be cross verified by the doctors and can be assigned as approved or dis-approved by them just as like button
        in facebook.\n\n

        Communication:\n\t
        For the convenience of communication problems, we can included calling, emails and messaging features.\n\t
        The doctors will get notifications for all the prescriptions submitted by the patients in those categories selected by the doctor.\n\n

        Map:\n\t
        Patients can see nearby hospitals and doctors available.  Travel agencies and food courts.\n\t
        Doctors can see the patients that are presently in their range.\n\t
        Colour code for the level of emergency.\n\n

        Prescription:\n\t
        Clients i.e. patients will give their details of problems which can be only seen by the doctors.\n\n

        Report:\n\t
        User can only see this. It will be edited only by the doctor. They can mention the medicines and other tests that they will prescribe which can be
        checked by the AI and machine learning procedures.\n\n\n


        Check us for more updates. See you soon !!</string>
</resources>
